"To work you have the right,
but not to the fruits thereof."
Author Unknown, "Bhagavad Gita"
Missed Call
Send
Save as draft
Send message?
Sending
Message sent
"I'd like to meet you after class and talk."
"And what are you calling me for?"
Doesn't he know what day today is?!
Nothing serious.
I just got the urge to call, that's all.
Anyway, I'm fine with meeting up,
but can we do it early?
Sending
3rd Season
Classroom
of
the
Elite
Classroom of
the Elite
Hey, Ayanokoji!
Did you get any chocolate?
Chocolate?
Translation: he wants to know
if you got any from Horikita.
Idiot! It's got nothing to do with Suzune!
So? You get any?
I haven't gotten any.
I don't expect to get any.
You serious?
Yes.
Yeah, I'll bet!
She'd never give you any, right?
Chocolate is nothing.
I can do without it, myself.
Don't act tough.
Wait, Sotomura, what happened to
your old-timey speech pattern?!
Oh, so you noticed.
Our recent meditation training
made me realize my true self,
so I left that old character beh—
How about you, Hondo?
Hey, listen to my answer!
Zero for me.
I hope I can get at least one.
You want it from Shinohara, right?
Wh-Why would you say that?!
Why would you bring up Shinohara?!
Well, you're always talking and stuff.
Shinohara's got a soft
spot for you, right, Ike?
We're not always talking!
I don't like her like that.
Just admit it, man. You like her, right?
N-No!
I get it!
The girls are just feeling shy,
so they haven't started handing
out their chocolate yet.
Maybe!
We might still have a chance!
Whoops...
Morning, everyone.
Amazing.
I guess they're not just feeling shy.
He breaks up with Karuizawa
and immediately gets this?
What?
How have things been with Kushida?
What do you mean?
Are they going well?
I'm not sure.
I'm still working hard to
improve our relationship.
Interested in helping?
Just asking.
I thought so.
However...
Kushida-san has been
changing, little by little.
She agreed to join me at the
Keyaki Mall café today after class.
Even though she usually turns
me down flat when I ask...
Really?
I believe we can talk this out rationally.
I'm glad to hear it.
You sound so detached.
As if it doesn't concern you...
Suzune?
Yes?
Um...
When can I come by for study help?
You're being unusually assertive today.
Well, sure I am.
I don't wanna be expelled.
S-So I thought, maybe today—
No.
We can start after clubs conclude.
We'll still have time then.
Yeah, figures.
According to Karuizawa's report,
Ichinose stayed home again today.
I was wondering who that was.
The first-years are having a
secret meeting at this hour, too?
Get out of my way.
I'm not without fondness for
people like you, you know.
Though my student council
wouldn't be the place for you.
Now, Horikita-senpai,
to get down to brass tacks...
You want to discuss this
in front of the first-year?
I don't see a problem.
I want you to sit out the exam tomorrow.
I'm sure you're aware that I can't do that.
You haven't anticipated my next move.
Rather...
There's not a single student in this school
who can anticipate what I'm thinking.
That includes your personal favorite.
Oh, that's right...
You were in the same group as
that first-year, weren't you?
Ayanokoji Kiyotaka.
The man of whom Horikita
Manabu thinks most highly...
And if Ayanokoji was involved
in Ryuen's downfall, then...
Maybe I'm overthinking it?
He doesn't look like a man with many layers.
It's so cold!
Why did we have to meet up here?
There've gotta be better places!
Karuizawa?
We can't exactly meet up in the lobby.
Even if you have broken up with Hirata,
it could give rise to unsavory rumors.
You wouldn't want that, would you?
I guess not.
But doesn't sneaking around
make it seem more fishy?
If anyone spots us,
it'll totally lead to rumors.
No worries there.
Sheesh, you're cautious about some
things and not at all about others...
Fine, then.
Still, it's freezing out here!
I wish it could just be summer already!
When summer comes, you'll just say,
"I wish it could be winter," won't you?
That's just how girls work, okay?
What are they talking about?
Karuizawa is the one Ayanokoji's
secretly been contacting?
So? Why'd you call me out today specifically?
It could have been any day, actually...
Really?
I thought there might be a specific
reason you asked to see me today...
No, there's just something
I wanted to confirm ASAP.
Does this number ring any bells for you?
Not sure who it could be...
They're not on my contact list.
Why don't you just call them back?
I've tried several times,
but their phone was turned off.
Is it important? Want me to start digging?
Yeah.
That's what I wanted to speak to you about.
But don't be careless about it, all right?
You got it.
Is that all you wanted?
Actually...
Wh-What?
Are you feeling confident about finals?
I expect them to be rather difficult.
For real?
Hey... you mind tutoring me?
Maybe not?
I can't allow you into our study group.
We'd need late-night sessions.
Would that be acceptable?
It's better than getting expelled!
True.
We'll set it up, then.
See you then!
Yeah. See you later.
Uh, hey, wait!
So...
Can I give you a little quiz?
A quiz?
What day is today?
The answer seems so obvious,
I feel like it has to be wrong.
Don't overthink it.
Just give me your first impulse.
Valenti—
Yep, that's right.
For me?
I originally bought it for Yosuke-kun,
but there's no need for that now, so...
You prepared it for Hirata, then?
What, got a problem with that?
No, I was just thinking, you must prepare
for Valentine's Day a long time in advance.
I-I like to be prepared.
I'd made up my mind to break up,
but there was a chance that I
might still need it, you know?
Is that how it works?
Well, since you don't have any romantic
experience, I'm sure you wouldn't get it.
I suppose.
Here I thought you'd chosen today
'cause you wanted me to give you some.
Sorry. I wasn't thinking about that at all.
Out of curiosity, did you
get any from anyone else?
No, none.
Zero?!
Typical. You're a man cut out for zeroes.
I suppose.
But are you sure about this?
If you give it to me,
it won't be zero anymore.
Yeah, which would be
pretty pathetic in itself.
Think of me as your emergency backup.
And feel free to give me double as thanks!
Is that how it works?
You bet that's how it works.
Valentine's chocolate, huh?
If it's all romance stuff, I guess that's
about as interesting as it'll get.
No, wait...
By the way...
A-Anyway, I'll head home.
Hey there, you two.
3rd Season
Classroom
of
the
Elite
Classroom of
the Elite
Um...
Who's that?
Hashimoto from Class A.
We were in the same group
at the training camp.
A secret meeting in a place like this?
You're more than meets the eye, Ayanokoji.
There's nothing secret about it!
No need to hide it.
Today's Valentine's Day.
We weren't meeting up for Valentine's Day.
No, no, I can see you've got chocolate.
I was on my way to the library
when Karuizawa called me over.
Well, it amounts to the same thing.
I'm not sure I follow.
Do you have some issue with this?
Well, it's just strange, right?
Karuizawa's last boyfriend
was Hirata, you know.
Wanting Ayanokoji so bad you'd dump
a swell guy like Hirata for him...
That just piques the curiosity, you know?
Oh, sorry.
I think you've got the wrong idea about this.
Wrong idea?
Yeah.
I was originally gonna give it to Hirata-kun,
but throwing it out felt like a waste.
So I needed a random guy,
and I chose Ayanokoji.
You two seemed pretty friendly
for him to be a "random guy."
Sorry, I'm not buying it.
Huh? You just jump out here
and start accusing us...
What's your problem, anyway?
I just want to know the truth.
You might as well just be honest with him.
Trying to hide it like this
will make trouble later.
It would be worse if he thought
we were dating, wouldn't it?
Fine, I'll tell you, but you'd better
not spread this around, okay?
My lips are sealed.
I'm just handing it off to Ayanokoji-kun
so he can give it to the guy
I've really got my eye on.
So Ayanokoji is a go-between?
That's right. Get it?
So who's the chocolate really for?
Huh? You expect me to tell
that to some guy I just met?
Are you some kinda moron?
Well, I...
Well, fair enough.
Seriously, back off already.
Yeah, guess I misinterpreted.
Here I thought you two had
a special relationship.
It's not any of your business, so butt out.
Well...
It's not exactly not my business.
What's your problem?
I've liked you for a while now.
You should go out with me, Karuizawa.
I dunno who it is you've got your eye on now,
but you haven't told him
how you feel yet, right?
What are you talking about?
You really think I'd agree
to go out with you like this?
Love is unpredictable.
That's what makes it so interesting.
Okay. Well, I'm leaving.
H-Hey!
Huh?
Wait, I'm leaving, too!
What a cold fish.
What a creep!
Sorry, Ayanokoji.
I came in at an awkward time.
I'm fine with it.
There's a lot I wanted to ask you about.
Can I get your contact info?
Sure.
Thanks a bunch.
Well, I should head home for now.
Later, Ayanokoji!
Sure.
I certainly wasn't expecting to get five.
Airi
Haruka
I guess it's about time.
Yes?
It's me, Ichinose.
Ayanokoji.
Ayanokoji-kun?
What are you—
That sounds bad.
You have a cold?
Yeah. So it's not a great time.
I thought maybe you hadn't been eating well.
Can you keep rice porridge down?
But...
I'd rather no one see me out here.
Can you at least accept a check-in visit?
Hang on a minute.
You don't take no for an
answer, Ayanokoji-kun.
Sorry.
Here.
Thanks, I—
Sorry.
Are you all right?
Yeah.
Would you like to come inside?
Feeling better?
Yeah. Thanks a lot.
But... you really could have just called.
I wanted to talk in person.
Sorry to come so late.
Have you seen a doctor?
Yeah. They said it's a cold.
I see.
Sorry to make you wear a mask, too.
I don't want anyone catching my cold.
I'm feeling quite a lot better, though...
I think the oversleeping and under-eating
is doing most of the damage at this point.
And this... rice porridge? Did you make it?
Yeah.
I see.
I can't remember the last time I ate.
You need to eat proper meals.
Right.
I can't remember the last time
I saw anyone in person, either.
Really?
A bunch of my friends came by to
see me, but I turned them away.
After that, I think they were
convinced I was depressed,
so they stopped trying.
Did you want to talk to me in person
because you were worried
that I was taking off
because of the rumors?
I appreciate it.
I'd never skip school because
of some silly rumors, though.
You're a strong person.
I'm not sure about "strong"...
She puts on a strong front,
but emotional stress can have a
demeritorious effect on the immune system.
Well, you shouldn't stay too long.
You'll catch my cold.
Yeah. I'm sorry for keeping you up, too.
Not at all. Thanks for visiting.
Yeah. Don't overdo it, okay?
That should do it.
Hey, are you kidding me?
What in the world?!
Wh-Who could have done this?
You all got it, too?
This is nuts!
Is this stuff true?
That's awesome!
Let's all have a study meeting to prepare for the test!
Ayanokoji Kiyotaka has a crush on Karuizawa Kei
Hondo Ryotaro is only into fat girls
I had no idea.
This is too damn mean!
Ayanokoji Kiyotaka has a crush on Karuizawa Kei
Hondo Ryotaro is only into fat girls
Shinohara Satsuki was a prostitute in middle school
By the time I got to class,
it was already everywhere...
Shinohara Satsuki was a prostitute in middle school
Sato Maya hates Onodera Kayano
They can't do this to me!
Hey, Sato, you hate Onodera?
I-I do not!
This is all made up!
I guess I'd better ask Onodera
if she knows what it's about.
H-Hey! Don't do that!
But if it's not true, it's okay to ask, right?
That's awful, Yamauchi-kun!
Shut up!
Knock it off already, man!
I just wanna confirm if it's made up or not.
Hey, Hondo!
Is yours true, too?
Ayanokoji!
It says you're into Karuizawa!
I'm not.
Aw, you're not?
That's boring.
The message board is awash with ugly rumors.
There's one about you, too.
Shi-no-ha-ra!
You were a prostitute?!
I was not!
Yamauchi, knock it off already!
C'mon, don't hide it!
This is stupid!
It's just a bunch of made-up rumors!
Maybe you wrote them yourself!
Huh? It wasn't me!
Enough! Just come clean already!
Who wrote these rumors?!
You know what they say.
"Where there's smoke, there's fire."
Just shut up!
I mean, the real problem is the
people getting written about, right?
Like, seriously.
Come clean already.
Yamauchi!
Wait!
Yamauchi, you knock it off, too.
Aw, c'mon.
Shinohara's always so stuck-up.
This is our chance to get some payback.
Payback?!
She said it wasn't true!
No way to know that.
It's always the plain girls like her
who've done the nastiest stuff.
It's not true!
I didn't do it.
Knock it off already!
Aw, you're no fun.
But Sato-san really doesn't like
Onodera-san very much, does she?
H-Hey, stop it, Miyamoto-kun!
Yeah, we don't see you two
hanging out very often, do we?
Th-That's just...
This is horrible.
After we'd finally achieved
some measure of class unity...